Academic Relations Office fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- SFU Childcare Society files, 1982 - 1987; F-203-8; 15 cm of textual records; Simon Fraser University Childcare Society
  - SFU Childcare Society, vol. 3, 1984 - 1985; F-203-8-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 203-13)
    File reviewed for access: Nov 24, 2021 (ML). File includes documents containing the personal information of identifiable individuals: employment and educational history.
  - Salary survey, 1985; F-203-8-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 203-13)
    File reviewed for access: Nov 24, 2021 (SM). Enclosure created for one document that contains the personal information of identifiable individuals: employment history.
  - SFU Childcare Society, vol. 1, 1985 - 1987; F-203-8-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 203-13)
  - SFU Childcare Society, vol. 2, 1985 - 1987; F-203-8-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 203-13)
  - Budget projections, 1986; F-203-8-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 203-3)
  - SFU Childcare Society, vol. 1, 1986; F-203-8-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 203-3)
  - SFU Childcare Society, vol. 2, 1986; F-203-8-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 203-3)